♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey Lois, can I please
have another pancake?
What? What's so funny?
I don't know.
Dog eating pancakes.
It's funny.
Mom, I need a check
for the school field trip.
Geez, Meg, didn't I just
take you on a field trip?
Okay, here's the field!
Good-bye forever!
Aah! Meg, I'm injured!
Please help me!
I smell gas!
Meg, I'm still alive,
but I'm badly burned!
Come save my life and
nurse me back to health!
Oh, God, why do bad things
happen to good people?!
Here, sweetie, I'll
write you a check.
No, no, I got it, Lois.
Let me just lick my thumb
'cause that's what people do
before they write a check.
Okay, now let me tilt my glasses
down and ask the date.
What's the date today?
Dad, why don't your checks
have any writing on them?
Why don't your shelves
have any trophies on 'em?
I've obviously
caught you at a bad time.
Lois, why don't my checks
have any writing on them?
Well, Peter...
What?
That's just a wide pad
of Post-its I gave you.
What?!
So that million dollar check
you gave me yesterday
is no good?
I quit my job, man!
I will not see you Monday!
What the hell, Lois?
Why don't I have
a real checkbook?
Peter, where do
checks come from?
Uh... when a mommy and daddy
love each other?
That's why.
Lois, I want my own checkbook,
and I want it now!
Ooh, I like
when Dad talks tough.
He sounds like
Dirty Harry.
You got to ask yourself
one question.
"Do I feel lucky?"
Well, do ya, punk?
Oh, Mr. Harry,
you're really not gonna like
what I have to say.
Hi. What can I
do for you?
Yes, I was wondering,
where is the room
where I can roll around nude
with my money?
I'm sorry?
No, I'm sorry.
I thought this was a bank.
I'll handle this.
My husband wants to
open a checking account.
Okay, well, first,
I'll need to see a photo I.D.
and a birth certificate.
Of course.
I keep all my important
papers in my bosom.
Okay, "Justin...
Peter... Griffin."
It's actually
just Peter Griffin.
So, this is not your
birth certificate?
Oh, my God!
Your first name
is Justin?!
It is?!
Wow, I never noticed that!
"Justin Griffin."
Huh, I like
the sound of that.
I'm a Justin!
This is awesome!
This changes everything!
Peter, it doesn't
change a thing.
You're still
the exact same person.
I beg to differ.
And now, international news
from Al Jarreau Jazeera.
♪ Car bombing in Syria ♪
♪ Skididdly boom-bop
a Dee, yeah ♪
♪ 37 people killed ♪
♪ Ooh, the people
are dead. ♪
Hey, Lois, you seen
my hiking boots?
I need 'em later
for park soccer.
Peter, why the hell
do you look like that?
Uh, my name
isn't Peter.
My name is Justin.
I'm living a Justin lifestyle,
and so is my family.
You want to go to
a concert? Huh?
Want to go to a
loud concert?
No.
Since I'm your cool
father Justin,
we should bond with
skin-to-skin contact.
How about Justin
takes his shirt off,
and we can get some photos
of you on Justin's belly?
Your heartbeat is weird.
It is not
consistent at all.
Okay, let's go for a
ride in my open Jeep.
I took the doors off,
so it's extra terrifying.
Geez, this "Justin" phase
of Dad's is kind of weird.
Eh, not as weird as
his karaoke phase.
Peter, did you throw up
in the sink?
Peter?
♪ ♪
♪ Out here
in the fields ♪
Yeah, that was me, I was the one
who threw up in the sink.
♪ I farm
for my meals... ♪
Dad, what are you
doing in here?
Oh, hey, Chris.
I just figured now
that I'm Justin,
I should start
a "Sweet News" wall
for stuff I think
is totally sweet.
Big puffy clouds
are very sweet.
Big hamburgers.
Small hamburgers, too.
Sliders, I think
they're called.
Ranch.
Here's just a
picture of a vest.
Pretty sweet.
Palm trees are very sweet,
'cause, like, the beach.
This is my room, Dad.
The band Guster is the
sweetest band of all time.
It was tough, 'cause I had
to move all my O.A.R. stuff
to fit the Guster stuff.
Peter, get out
of Chris's room.
Oh, hey Mama.
Hey, you seen my copy
of Into the Wild?
I like to have it on
my person at all times,
in case I need a
quick "inspo sesh."
Oh, did I tell you I'm gonna
be doing a lot of abbreve's?
Peter, you sound
like an idiot.
And did you put a skateboard
in the washing machine?
It's gonna cost several
hundred dollars to repair.
How we do, Lois.
All we do.
You ever get in the
pocket of a wave?
Peter, you know
I haven't.
And I know for a fact
that you haven't, either.
In the pocket.
Some gnarlies out there.
Some "gnar-gnars."
Was in one today.
It's like the rest of
the world just shuts off,
and all that matters
is you and Lady Blue.
And you know what
she said to me?
"You're great."
Keep it cool, Lois.
K-E-W-L.
So, you want to
go upstairs?
Sure.
Great.
Go.
Hey, Justin, I wanted
to introduce you to Keira.
She's the one who brought
four loose Sierra Nevadas.
Keira!
You totally rock
for bringing those.
Peter, what the hell
is going on?!
Oh, dude, is that your mom?
No, I'm not his mom,
you little bastard.
That "little bastard" knows how
to smoke pot out of an apple.
All right,
everyone out of here.
I've had enough of
this "Justin" nonsense.
Tomorrow we're
going to city hall
to legally change your
name back to "Peter."
All right, fine.
But I got to say, being Justin
was quite an adventure.
Like when I found
where the Wild Things were.
I owe you, Max.
You led me right to 'em.
All right, now help me grind
their horns into boner pills.
Keira, that was
an amazing night.
Sorry I can't
drive you to work.
I gotta go sit in my
den until you leave.
Oh, that's okay.
I'll just take
the school bus.
Wait... what?!
You-you drive
a school bus?
No, silly,
I take the bus.
I'm in high school.
What the hell?!
You said you were 23!
Yeah, and you said
you loved me.
Well, I guess you
got me there.
Hey, Quagmire,
sorry to bother you,
but we're following up
on a tip.
Did you have sex
with this underage girl?
I don't want to go to jail, but
I really want to take credit.
Quagmire, I'm afraid you're
under arrest for statutory rape.
All right, but let me
just send the pictures
I took of her last night
to all my friends.
Oh, yeah!
Boom!
You're disgusting.
Take him away.
We've got all the awesome
evidence we need.
"Hello, my name is
Glenn Quagmire.
"I am a neighbor of yours
on Spooner Street.
I am here to inform you
that I am a sex offender."
It seems as though you could
have had some of that memorized.
Glenn, what the
hell's going on?
It turns out
that girl I took home
from Peter's party last night
is in high school.
Oh, my God!
Does this mean you're gonna move
to Europe to make movies?
How in the world did you
not know she was underage?
Well, in retrospect,
she did ask a lot of questions
about To Kill a Mockingbird.
Should have sent
her my way.
I love that book.
Oh, Gregory Peck-- whew!
Anyway, now I gotta
go in front of a judge.
Really?
Number one or number two?
Our judicial system
is so broken.
No, Peter-- Glenn
has to go to court.
That's right.
And there's not even a defense
for statutory rape.
Once the girl proves her age,
that's it-- you're guilty.
You know what
I tried today?
A fig.
I have a hearing
tomorrow morning.
I may have
to go to jail.
My only hope for leniency is
to bring in character witnesses
and show the court I'm not
the monster they say I am.
Well, Peter would be
happy to support you.
Yeah, you betcha,
Quagmire.
I'm very persuasive.
That's why I was so good
at selling low-cost
car insurance.
White-trash rates
from an army guy.
Here is a penguin,
don't know why.
The General Car Insurance.
It'll worry whoever you hit.
I can't believe Quagmire
and that girl had sex.
Which is hugging someone
really hard with your legs.
Nope.
Well, you'll tell me
if I get it, though, right?
Yeah, I'll tell
you if you get it.
Okay, I'm gonna
get it.
Now, Mr. Griffin,
I understand you're here
to speak
on Mr. Quagmire's behalf.
That's right,
Your Honor.
And as we know, according
to Game of Thrones,
if the girl has had her
blood, she is good to go.
Has the girl had her blood?
Answer the question.
Mr. Griffin, she was underage.
Yes, however, Mr. Quagmire
was born on February 29th.
Ergo, he's only 12.
Ergo, the girl raped him.
Argo, Ben Affleck.
Mr. Griffin,
do you have any evidence
that is not based
on film or television?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask
all these letters
to Santa Claus?
Something's going on.
We haven't gotten
mail in a week.
I-- I haven't gotten
Nobody writes you.
Officer Swanson, I'll remind you
that you are under oath.
Now, please tell us
what Mr. Quagmire said
he did with the girl.
He, uh,
said he gave her a Frosty Jim.
And can you please
explain to the courtroom
what a Frosty Jim is.
Uh...
Sir, you're under oath.
Well, it's when you
urinate in a condom,
and tie it off, freeze it,
and then the woman, um,
pretends it's a man.
Thank you.
He's a good guy!
Mr. Brown, can you please state
your occupation for the court?
Aw, come on, man, you didn't
ask anyone else to do that!
Why am I on trial?!
He's the one that mushed
hisself on a child!
When are we gonna see
this chick?
Okay, enough! No more help!
I'm taking this Bible.
You want to know what kind
of person Glenn Quagmire is?
You want to know
what made me the person I am?
Then put me on the stand.
Lois, can I play
Angry Birds on your phone?
Okay, but only
with the sound off.
Fine. I'll just do it
with my mouth.
Pa-shooo!
Please, go ahead,
Mr. Quagmire.
Look, I know everyone's sitting
out there judging me today.
But before you do, please know
I had it pretty
rough growing up.
My dad was a military man,
so he wasn't around much.
And my mom, well,
let's just say,
she was a little promiscuous.
In fact, I think my problems
started the day I was born.
Wah! Wah! Wah!
It's a boy,
Mrs. Quagmire.
Oh, that's wonderful!
How do you feel?
Horny. Really horny.
Could you put him back
so I can push him out again?
I was born nine times that day.
And things never got easier.
The only way I learned
my ABC's was by learning
the names of all the guys
my mom slept with.
♪ Art, Bob, Chet,
Don, Ed, Frank, Gus ♪
♪ Hal, Irv, John, Ken,
Lew-Matt-Ned-Ox-Pat ♪
♪ Quint, Ron, Sam,
Tom, Ulf, Vic ♪
♪ Walter, Xavier,
Yaz and Zeke ♪
♪ Those are just
some of the guys ♪
♪ There are lots
of other guys. ♪
It was awful.
I didn't even get to go
to my high school prom.
But my mom did.
Hey, is Crystal ready?
Oh, hi, Ronnie.
Hey, listen, have my mom
home by midnight, okay?
How about I plow her in the limo
and have her home in 20 minutes?
Ah, come on, Ronnie,
she bought the dress.
So, you see, Your Honor,
thanks to my mom,
I never had a chance to
be like everyone else.
My misguided carnal instincts
are the result
of being raised
by a sexual deviant.
All I'm asking is
that you give me
the break that
my childhood never did.
Dairy Queen closes
in ten minutes.
Mr. Quagmire,
your story is a sad one,
but that doesn't
excuse your actions.
I have no choice but to sentence
you to 20 years in prison.
Oh, no you don't!
Mom?!
Crystal?
Ha! She's enjoyed many men.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Do you know I'm carrying
three handguns,
and the metal detectors
picked up nothing?
Your Honor,
as the defendant's mother,
I ask that you show
mercy on him.
Well, as the victim's mother,
I ask that you go to hell!
Where is
your daughter?
Show her to us!
Your Honor,
I have renounced my sinful past,
and have been washed
in the blood
of the Lord Jesus Christ.
You what?!
I have seen
the righteous path
of our Savior,
and ask that you
not sentence my son to jail,
but instead release him
to my custody so that I,
with God's guidance,
can rehabilitate him.
Wow, Quagmire's mom is
a Jesus freak.
I haven't been
this surprised since we went
to that restaurant
on my birthday.
All right, guys, let's pay
the check and get out of here.
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
You guys!
♪ Happy Birthday, dear Peter ♪
♪ Happy Birthday to you. ♪
Aren't you gonna blow out
your candles, Peter?
Mom, I think something's
wrong with Dad.
Peter? Peter?!
Oh, my God! Help!
Someone call 911!
It's okay, ma'am.
This happens here at
Bennigan's all the time.
How long does this last?
Hard to say.
It's best to just move on.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Quagmire,
but my sentence stands.
20 years.
Mr. Quagmire,
I'll give you 24 hours
to get your affairs in order.
Oh, my God.
Ah, don't think
of it as 20 years.
Think of it
as two ten-year-olds,
you sick freak.
God, 20 years.
I know this is
a hard time for you,
but you need
to seek forgiveness.
You need to kneel before Jesus.
Oh, he's gonna be kneeling
in front of a lot of guys,
but I doubt
he'll catch their names.
It's usually somebody pushing
your skull in the dark.
There are really
no introductions.
Remember, He is
inside you all the time.
Oh, n-now she's
just setting me up.
Right?
How dare you come in here
and tell me to seek forgiveness!
Where do you get off?!
Pretty much
everywhere, I hear.
Fat man's right--
they're making this easy.
You've never apologized once
for the way you raised me!
You're the one who
made me what I am!
Oh, come on, Quagmire,
you're a grown man,
responsible for his own choices.
Seems kind of cowardly to blame
someone else for your problems.
Brian abandoned
his own son, by the way.
Why are you, of all people,
defending a religious nut?
Aren't you an atheist?
Yeah, it's crazy.
You can think about that
while you're in jail.
Glenn, we're not
going to get anywhere
questioning God's wisdom.
He has a plan for everything.
Oh, now I get it.
That's why you found God.
So you can absolve yourself
of any responsibility
and answer everything
with empty platitudes.
Face it, you're a worse parent
than Brad Pitt
and Angelina Jolie.
I'm concerned about Pax,
Maddox, and Shiloh.
They're having
trouble adapting.
They've been raised
with 11 languages,
and really don't speak any.
I hear you, Doctor.
So... you're saying we should
give them all faux-hawks?
No. I think they need
intensive therapy.
Let me see if I understand you.
Even shorter on the sides?
Don't you see?
This is your chance to open
your heart and let God in.
I know this jail sentence
seems long.
But salvation can
last all eternity.
You know what else
lasts an eternity?
This conversation.
And maybe through our shared
relationship with the Lord,
we can begin to build
a bond as mother and son.
"Mother and son"?!
Mothers love their children!
They nurture them
and protect them!
You've never done
a thing for me!
I'd rather rot in
jail than sit here
and listen to all your crap!
Glenn's right.
I was never there for him.
I've got to find
some way to fix this.
Did you hear about
your ex-husband yet?
He had a... uh, procedure.
You know, some families take
their baby to the zoo.
That's also a fun activity.
I'm really gonna
miss all you guys.
And I'll think of you whenever
I choke on a link sausage.
Take care, buddy.
Oh, yeah!
Fresh air! Freedom!
Peter, while I'm away,
I want you to hold onto my
antique, gold Rolex watch.
Oh cool, a throwing watch!
No, no, Peter, it--
and I cannot stress
this enough--
it is not a throwing watch.
Oh, I hear you, Quagmire.
It didn't come back,
like you said it would.
And-and Joe, you
sure you don't mind
taking care of my cat?
Oh, no, all taken care of.
Brought her
to the pound this morning.
She went peacefully.
What?! No!
I-I-I meant, take care of
her, like, look after her!
Well, that seems like
a note for this morning.
You know, maybe I won't miss
you people as much as I thought.
Do you have anything
for me, Glenn?
What? No! Wha-what?!
I just found out my cat died!
Hmm. I can't help but think
this selfish attitude
is part of what got you here.
Good-bye, Glenn. Be strong.
We'll keep you in our thoughts.
Oh, y-you better get rid of that
before you get in there.
All right.
Good-bye, everybody.
And-and don't worry about me.
I-I'll see you real soon.
Hey, you guys take good care
of my child rapist friend!
Mr. Quagmire, wait!
Judge?!
What are you doing here?
I wanted to tell you
the good news in person.
Your sentence
has been commuted.
You will not be serving
prison time after all.
You got a good body, man.
Why do you hide it
under that robe?
"Commuted"?
I don't understand.
Hello, Glenn.
Mom?!
What's going on here?
By the way, Your Honor,
your fly is down.
Well, let's just say some
new DNA evidence was produced.
And an impressive amount,
I'd say.
Guy takes care of himself.
Anyway, you're free to go.
You... you're kidding!
Mom... Di-did you...?
Yep. Twice.
But I-I thought you
were Christian now.
Helping my son is the most
Christian thing I could do.
You were right, Glenn.
I was a terrible mother.
I wasn't there for you
when I should've been.
But I'd love a second chance.
I'd like that.
I'd like that very much.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
Aw, Quagmire got away with it,
and learned nothing.
That's great.